What gives?
何だ　こりゃ
This wasn't any fun! It sucked!
つまらねえ
しまらねえ
I didn't expect to wipe 'em out
with this lame performance.
この程度の演奏で全滅するとは思わなかった
You out-classed them, Master.
師匠はお洒落だから
Yup! I compare gunfights
to music 'cause I'm classy.
そう　俺は洒落ているから銃撃戦を音楽に例える
You fled all the way from Italy
はるばるイタリアから
地球か火星なのか見分けもつかねえとこまで逃げてきやがって
to some place where I can't
even tell if it's on Earth or Mars!
Where is this, Chinatsu?
ここどこだっけ　千夏
The tip of Oman in the Middle East.
中東　オマーンの飛び地だよ
I was thinkin' while we hunted you down,
こう思いながら追った
"This is a group of morons, but they've got guts!"
「すげえバカだがすげえ根性がある連中だ」
"I'm gonna get to put on an epic
concert worthy of becomin' legendary!"
だからきっと伝説になるような名演奏を奏でられる
I overestimated you.
買いかぶったぜ
Even the fish I catch put up more of a fight!
釣られた魚でももうちょっとは抵抗する
O-Orchestra...
オ　オーケストラ
Go on, Chinatsu. Ask him.
ほら　千夏
こいつに聞けよ
は　何を
Ask what?
Don't gimme that!
何をじゃないよ
If a top dog in the mafia like this
bozo steals from his boss and runs,
マフィア幹部ほどのそいつがボスの金奪って逃げたら
俺たち殺し屋に追われるのはわかりきったことって
he knows that hit men like us
are gonna come after him, right?
ほれ
Oh, yeah. You knew how this
would end, yet you did it anyway.
ああ　そう
結末は分かってたのに
それでもやっちゃった
Why?
何で
Tell me why!
教えてよ
This brat's eyes...
このガキ　なんて目を
I don't know. I forgot.
さあね
忘れちまった
Now then, can you answer my question?
それより俺の質問いいか
Hmn?
うん
Why aren't you wearing panties?
You're a disgusting pervert!
どうしてパンツはいてねんだ
気持ちわりー変態め
殺し屋って奴ら理解不能のくそだぜ
Hit men are incomprehensible pieces of shit!
Go to Hell!
死ね
This one didn't answer us, either.
また答えてもらえなかったな
残念
Alas, you're the one who's goin' to Hell!
死ぬのはお前だよ
But don't expect it to be quick.
だが　楽に死ねると思うなよ
The order was to "inflict unimaginable pain."
「あらん限りの苦痛をもって」と注文を受けてる
My job is to shatter naïve dreams like,
"I'll be the only one to get away,"
あたしの仕事は
「自分だけは逃げ切れる」みたいな甘い確信犯の夢を
from people who commit premeditated crimes.
めちゃめちゃに粉砕すること
畜生　てめえら
Damn you, freaks!
Do you know what this is?
これ　分かるか
Well, it's like a music box.
まあ　オルゴールみたいなもんだ
Chinatsu's good at makin' contraptions like this.
千夏はこういう工作が得意でな
Bang! Bang, bang!
It's a device that shoots
all of the bullets in one spot.
全弾を一ヵ所に撃ち込む装置なのだ
太腿のお肉が全部吹っ飛ぶぞ
It'll send the flesh on your thigh flying!
I'm going to kill you!
てめえら　ぶっ殺す
止めろ　こら
--Don't do this, dammit!
--Later!
じゃあな
Cut the crap!
ふざけんな
Orchestra!
オーケストラ
Wait, Orchestra!
待ってくれよ　オーケストラ
You won't get off--
てめえら絶対に
Oh, he has a pretty nice singing voice.
なかなかいい声で歌うじゃないか
So what's next, Master?
これからどうするの　師匠
Since we've come all this way,
let's get in another job.
せっかく遠出したんだ
もうひと仕事しようぜ
Think there are any?
あるかな
Spring's a profitable time for us hired guns.
春の終わりは殺し屋の稼ぎ時
No one wants to carry future
headaches into the friggin' hot summer.
誰だって　頭痛の種をくそ暑い夏に持ち越したくはない
Oh, uh-huh.
By the way, Chinatsu...
ところで千夏
Why aren't you wearing any panties?
何でパンツはいてないんだ
That's a secret.
秘密
Want me to mesmerize you?
悩殺されたい
Stupid! You couldn't turn me on
even if you were bare-butt naked!
バカめ
たとえすっ裸で歩こうがピクリともこねえよ
'Course that's another matter for mature women.
熟女なら話は別だがな
At any rate, let's go to the city.
とにかく　都会に行こう
Yep.
そうだね
We have always stood on the borderland.
I'm enjoying the view from here.
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
much the same
We have always stood on the borderland.
日听   yaya
I'm enjoying the view from here.
日听      奶昔
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
I don't want to lose,
but I don't want to hurt anyone either
时轴      小瑾
I took it so I could confirm
手に取って　確かめてた
That there's definitely no going back
きっと戻れないんだって
Whose side are you on?
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Memories are shackles
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
注释   TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) A postscript love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
后期  aoi
(Don't want to know!) Your kindness is a disservice
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
We have always stood on the borderland.
压制   娜夏
With your arms out wide, keep balanced
広げる両手　keep balance
Go the direction that lets you fly higher
より高く飛べる方へ
I want to protect
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
What our wingless backs here bore:
Reality & Dream
Reality and Dream
ヨナ
Jonah, there's a lot you need to
learn from your elders in life.
君は我々人生の先輩から学ばなければならないことがたくさんあるぞ
First, there are the various greetings,
from "Good morning" to "Good night."
まずはおはようからおやすみまで各種挨拶
You need language studies, math, science,
social studies, and a general education!
語学　数学　理科　社会
一般教養
英語はなかなかのもんなんだけどね
But your English is already pretty impressive.
こら　授業中にあくびしない
Watch it! No yawning during class.
君は元少年兵だ
You are an ex boy soldier.
私の部隊に来た以上
Since you've joined my unit,
素敵な人間にステップアップしなければならない
you must level up and become a wonderful human!
ほかの八人は一癖もふた癖もあるが
Everyone has a quirk or two,
but they are all extremely skilled!
各人とても優秀なのである
O-Okay then! Give the next problem a try.
よ　よし　じゃあ次の計算やってみろ
It's roughly 300.
だいたい三百くらいだ
算数で「だいたい」はダメ
"Roughly" doesn't cut it in math!
こ　この前はびっくりしちゃったよね
Y-You really shocked us
the other day at the airport.
空港で
タイヤがたくさん付いてる
It has a lot of tires.
二十二個付いています
It has 22 tires.
So, what is the total number
of tires on those three airplanes?
それではあの三機の飛行機のタイヤは
全部でいくつですか
あれ　えらく長く考えるなあ
Huh? This is taking him a while.
A lot.
たくさんだ
それなんだ　ココ
What is that, Koko?
ん　これ
Oh, this? A hit man list.
ヒットマンリスト
HQ warns us of any dangerous thugs in the area.
私たちの近くにいる危険人物を本部が警告してくれる
Naturally, this is only the tip of the iceberg.
もちろんこんなの氷山の一角だけどね
But this city is really good at keeping the peace,
まあ　この町の治安はすっごくいいから
so there isn't much point
in warning us about hit men.
殺し屋に気をつけると言われてもね
Besides, I've got you guys to protect me.
貴方たちが守ってくれるしね
They're called Orchestra with just two members?
たった二人でオーケストラ
そう　初めは八人いて　七人死んだの
Right. There were originally eight, but seven died.
They just got a new member,
making it a team of two.
最近一人入って二人組に
Orchestra was treacherous during its prime.
最盛期のオーケストラはヤバかった
They shot 20,000 rounds
at a police force in France.
フランスで警官隊を相手に二万発撃った
ココは殺し屋に狙われてるの
Koko, hit men are after you?
Always. Arms dealers tend to make enemies.
常に
武器商人は恨みを買う
I've made so many that
I'd love to sell their grudges!
買いすぎてそろそろ売りたいけど
But no one would buy them!
誰一人として買ってくれない
What's going on?
何だ何だ
ヨナ坊の勉強中かと思ったら
I thought Jonah was in the middle of studying,
but you seem to be having a blast!
ずいぶん楽しそうだな
もう　楽しそうってね
Jeez, don't give me that!
You're all mature adults,
いい大人がせっかくのオフに部屋の中でごろごろ
yet here you are lazing about
the room on your day off!
え　このホテル　居心地いいしさ
This hotel is just so comfy!
In that case, Koko, why don't we go on a date?
それではココ
私とデートしましょう
Okay! I'd like to show Jonah around town,
オッケー
ヨナ　にも
街を見せて歩きたいけども
but math comes first!
やっぱり算数が大事だ
頑張ろう
Good luck!
Sorry about that, Tojo.
I'll get you a bunch of beer as souvenirs!
それじゃ　トージョ　悪いね
お土産にビールたくさんあげる
And Jonah, be sure to say,
"Thank you," at the end of class.
ヨナも授業終わったらちゃんと
「ありがとうございました」って言うんだよ
--Now, then...
--Nature calls.
さて
トイレ
Jonah?
ヨナ
Wha--?!
Wh-Why that little...
あ　あいつ
He's good at ditching class.
サボるの上手いな
It looks like we're going to have our hands full
これから皆てこずりそうだ
since we're each teaching him a different subject.
分担で教えるんだからなあ
え　突然イタリア語
You randomly went into Italian?! There a problem?
どうしたの
And what's with that lame hat?
それになんだ　そのイモ臭い帽子
It's blockin' your vision. Get rid of it!
視界の邪魔だろ　捨てちまえ
Master, you gave this hat to me,
so I can't throw it away.
この帽子は師匠がくれた物だから捨てないよ
Since you, like, look at the sky when
you walk, I look down at the ground.
そして師匠が空を見て歩くから
あたしは地面を見るのだ
He's cute.
可愛い
Isn't that boy with the silver hair cute?
あの男の子
銀の髪してて可愛いな
ほら師匠
Look, Master!
あ　いなくなった
Oh, he's gone...
Don't lose focus! We're about
to get ahold of our target.
気を散らすな
そろそろ目標を捕捉するぜ
Whoo boy! This is amazing!
これは素晴らしい
そしてさすが免税の国
I love duty-free countries!
ココの年齢の女の子なら
I think most girls Koko's age would
flip out over clothes and makeup.
服や化粧品に飛び付くと思うのですが
時計にしてもこのようなメカチックなものよりプリティーな
And they'd want a pretty
watch over a mechanical sic--
買おう
I'm buying it!
Koko, I'll buy it and give it to you as a present!
ココ　私が買ってプレゼントしましょう
え　そんな　バルメ　悪いよ
You shouldn't! I'd feel bad, Valmet.
デートしてくれたお礼です
It's my way of thanking you for the date.
No, it's a sign of my love!
っていうか愛の証です
Really? You're sure?!
ホントに　いいの
Yeah, totally!
ええ　もちろんです
あの顔は心底喜んでます
She looks genuinely thrilled! Sweet!
やった
You're a woman who lives off of selling weapons.
武器を売って生きる女
いつかは殺されると分かっているのに
You know that someday it will
get you killed, so why do it? Tell me!
なんで　教えてよ
殺し屋ごときが私に問うか
A lowly assassin has no right to ask that!
私を殺せたら教えてやる　オーケストラ
I'll tell you if you manage to kill me, Orchestra!
んだ　こいつ
What's with this chick?!
Let go of me!
放せよ
ココ
Koko!
Hey!
おいおい　何が降ってきやがった　千夏
Hey, now! What just fell from the sky, Chinatsu?!
Chinatsu, get back here!
千夏　下がれ
Keep firing at Ms. Eye Patch!
眼帯を撃ち続けろ
Roger!
了解
Annoying! Annoying, Ms. Eye Patch!
ウザ　ウザ
眼帯
Koko! Koko!
ココ  ココ
It happened so quickly that I can't say for sure,
一瞬でわかんなかったけど
but it looked like that cutie
from earlier fell from the sky.
落ちてきたの　さっきの可愛い子に見えたな
He protected the weapons dealer?
武器商人を守った
But dang, that Koko chick, like, ticks me off!
それにしてもむかつくのだ
ココとか言うやつ
She's, like, the type of woman I totally loathe!
超嫌いなタイプの女なのだ
I know exactly what you're thinkin', Chinatsu!
分かるぜ　千夏が考えてることよ
C'mon! It's time you
came on out, Lady Arms Dealer.
ほれ　そろそろ出てきて下さいよ
武器商人様よ
I'm terribly sorry that
you gotta deal with us hit men,
殺し屋ごときが相手で
大変申し訳ないが　楽しい音楽会はもう始まってるぜ
but the exuberant concert has already begun!
Kissy-poo!
ムチュウ
何するんだよ　ココ
What are you doing, Koko?!
Talk about nice timing, Jonah! Most impressive!
ナイスタイミングだよ　ヨナ
さすがだ
You've done this before.
この前もそうだった
Even when you were in a sticky
situation, you kept on smiling.
危ない目に遭ってるのに笑ってた
Don't fire!
撃つな
That's right. Nothing good
would come from shooting me.
そうだ 撃ってもロクなことないからな
どうかしてる
There's something wrong with you.
Now, now. Don't raise your head.
ほら　頭を上げるな
There's nothing wrong with me.
どうもしてないよ私は　ヨナ
Jonah, attacks on this level just
make me go, "Ah, not again!"
この程度の襲撃は
「ああまたか」って感じだ
A hired gun's bullets will hit when
they hit, no matter how hard you pray.
殺し屋の弾丸なんてね
どれだけ祈っても　当たる時は当たるし
And when they miss, they'll miss
even if you didn't want them to.
当たらない時は当たりたくても当たらないものよ
To top it off, I'm a weapons dealer.
まして私は武器商人
I'd never get anywhere if I was afraid of my wares.
商品にビビッてちゃお話にならない
I thought it was him!
やっぱりあの子だ
いるもんだな　悪い女って
There sure are some bad women out there.
I'm dying to blast her away right this second...
今すぐふっ飛ばしたくなってきたぞ
...with my Chinatsu Special Cannon.
「千夏キャノンスペシャル」で
おい　銃を捨てろ
Freeze! Drop your weapons!
Free--
Wow!
頭を引っ込めて
Get your head down!
よう　千夏
Hey, Chinatsu! This is turning into a masterpiece!
なかなかいい曲になってきたぜ
Oh, wow!
Master, look!
師匠　見て
立った
It's standing up!
That's cool, Chinatsu!
かっこいいじゃねえか　千夏
次の楽器出せ
Pull out the next instrument.
うん
Uh-huh!
--Koko, are you all right?
--Valmet!
ココ　怪我はありませんか
バルメ
That friggin' hurt!
いってーな
Valmet!
バルメ
That eye-patched chick is a pain in the ass!
邪魔クセェな　あの眼帯
いってい
Ow...
抜ける
It went through! Those bullets
can pierce through this shield!
この盾　弾が抜ける
Valmet!
バルメ
Valmet, are you okay?
バルメ　大丈夫
Yeah...
How did Valmet make a mistake like this?
何をヘマってんだ　バルメの奴
嫌な予感してたんだよね
I had a bad feeling about their excursion.
Can you hear me?
聞こえるか
アルシロップショッピングモールで襲撃を受けてる
We're under fire at the AI Shop Shopping Mall.
We're up against the two-man
team of killers, Orchestra.
相手は殺し屋オーケストラ二人組
Handguns won't cut it.
拳銃じゃラチがあかない
Bring my usual.
俺のいつものやつ持ってきて
Yeah, that's the one.
そう　それ
Lutz, climb the belfry.
ルツ　鐘楼に登れ
Take Wilee with you.
ワイリを連れてけ
Okay, now, everyone! Commence operations!
はいはい皆さん　状況開始ですよ
Valmet...
バルメ
I'm sorry, Koko. I don't think
I'm going to be of much help this time.
すみません　ココ
今回役に立てそうにないです
Don't sweat it. Lehm and the others will...
心配するな　レームたちが
ヨナ　ダメ　ヨナ
Jonah!
Don't, Jonah!
おもしれー
Bring it on, brat!
ガキ
Master!
師匠
Why'd you stop me, Chinatsu?
何で邪魔する　千夏
It'd be a shame to kill such a cutie!
あの子　可愛いからもったいない
ヨナ君一本釣り
I caught a Jonah!
What were you thinking, Lehm?! I almost had them!
何するんだレーム
あと少しで仕留められた
Calm down.
落ち着けよ
What gives? Normally you're such a gentleman,
どうした　いつもの紳士的な君が今まるで獣のようだぜ
but right now you're acting like an animal.
I'm sure you could have killed them,
確かに仕留められただろうよ
but at the cost of your own life.
だが君も死んでたね
Don't move to the same beat as those killers.
殺し屋の乗りに乗せられてんじゃねえよ
Ticked that I stopped you?
邪魔されてむかつくか
I'm even more ticked off!
俺はそれ以上にむかついてるぜ
That boy soldier fightin' style really pisses me off.
少年兵の戦い方ってのは本当に頭にくる
Remember this well:
いいか　覚えろ
We don't fight to the death.
うちは「殺し合い」なんてやらない
If we're gonna kill someone, it's one-sided.
やるとしたら一方的な「殺し」
You train like mad to master the techniques for
捨て身の突撃が必要な状況は
when you need to sacrifice
yourself and charge the enemy.
訓練に訓練を重ねたテクニックで補え
And then you put 'em
outta your mind, boy soldier.
そして忘れろ　少年兵を
Oh, but I think your stance
of hatin' weapon dealers is cool.
あ　でも俺　君の「武器商人を恨む」ってスタンスいいと思うんだよね
Why not spend your life soaking up our skills
技術を吸収しつつ
ココにも俺らにも飲み込まれないぞって生き方
while working to keep Koko and the
rest of us from drownin' out your views?
ありなんじゃねえ
師匠
Master!
The police's sniper unit, eh?
警察の狙撃班か
It's time to change locations.
場所の替え時だな
When you're that close...
そんくらいの距離
...you're within our range, too!
こっからでも届くっつの
If you wanna kill us, snipe from a kilometer away!
俺らをやりたきゃ一キロスナイパー持ってこい
Yeah!
Jonah! Lehm!
ヨナ　レーム
Jonah, we'll guide you and offer backup with this.
ヨナ
こいつで誘導して援護もする
Protect Koko while you flee
to safety. Can you handle that?
ココを守って逃げ回れ
できるか
Koko, don't let go of my hand.
ココ　手を離さないで
Roger.
了解
We're going!
行くよ
あ　くそ　防ぎやがった
Aw, dammit! She blocked it! This for real?
マジかよ
45-caliber bullets are heavy!
45口径は重いよ
And here my timing was
perfect for a surprise attack.
絶好の不意討のタイミングだったんだがね
いい勘してるぜ
She's got good intuition.
敵を褒めないでください　レーム
Please don't compliment the enemy, Lehm!
聞いたか千夏よ
Do you hear that sound, Chinatsu?
Some moron is using a silencer!
あの音
サイレンサーなんぞ付けてバカが
シケた音混ぜんじゃねー
Don't mix that dampened noise with my music!
こわー
Scary!
俺の音楽を打ち壊すもんかこの野郎
You tryin' to trash my music, bastard?!
Dumb old fart can't even read the mood!
空気読め　ジジが
Beat it, senile jerk!
引っ込んでろ　ボケ
Huh? Music? Don't make me laugh.
ああ　音楽だ
笑わせんな
You're the one who's gone senile.
ボケてんのはお前のほうだぜ
Has too much work made you forget?
Or are you just ignorant?
忘れたか
仕事のやりすぎで
それとも無知なのか
Gunfights are nothing more than farting contests.
銃撃戦なんてものは屁のこき合いだ
They're a far cry from music,
and somethin' to be ashamed of!
音楽にはほど遠い恥ずべき行為
"People of the world, I'm sorry to disturb you!"
「世間の皆様　お騒がせしてすみません」と
You should be thinkin' that while blushin' bright red.
赤面しながらやるもんだろが
ほう　おもしれー　結構吹くぜ　あのオッサン
Fascinating! That old fart's pretty good!
おっと　弾切れかよ
Uh oh. I'm out of bullets.
More importantly, that Koko lady
is making a run for it, Master!
それよりココって奴が逃げちゃってるよ　師匠
へ　気をつけろよ
Be careful, 'cause you're dead the
moment the weasel stops going, "Pop!"
鼬の最後っ屁すら出なくなったら
お前　死ぬぜ
Shut it! Die!
うるせー　死ね
そんな奴ほっといて
Screw that guy! Let's go, Master!
行こ　師匠
こういう時に　さっきの爆発する弾を撃てばいい
You should use those explosives at times like this.
I'm all out of 40mm and AK rounds!
40ミリもAKの弾ももうないよ
But we just bought that machine gun set.
その代わり　機関銃セットを買ったじゃない
お　そうだった　そうだった
Right! That's right!
We're up against so many targets this time
今回の標的は人数が多いからって
that we bought a super flashy weapon!
ド派手な武器を買ったぜ
Chinatsu, you really are the best!
やっぱり千夏は最高だ
You've put me back in high spirits!
俺はもうすっかり機嫌よくなっちまった
That's, like, the greatest compliment ever!
この上ない褒め言葉なのだ
That kid who fell from the sky
wasn't on the list, was he?
ところであの空飛んできたガキ
リストになかったよな
Damn that informant! Let's kill him later.
ふざけやがって情報屋
後でぶっ殺そう
超賛成
I agree big time!
テンガロンをかぶった小娘が
The girl in the ten-gallon hat is doing
a good job controlling that boar.
イノシシ男を上手く制御しています
You felt the same way?
バルメもそう思った
She's like a Weapon Direction System.
まるで武器管制システムだ
And she picks up on things like
radar, making them impregnable.
おまけにレーダーみたいに気を巡らせているから鉄壁だ
The girl in the ten-gallon hat...
テンガロンのほうが
....has some nasty skills.
能力的にヤバイ
We need to figure out a way to pull them apart.
何とか切り離しを考えないと
Hey! Tojo, swap out with Valmet.
よし　トージョ
バルメと替われ
Map! Guns! Radios!
マップ　銃　無線
パンチ力強いぞ
They pack quite the punch,
so look out for killer blows!
でかい一撃に注意しろ
Use frequency 817.
周波数　817
I've located Ms. Koko and Jonah,
as well as Wilee and Lutz.
ココさんとヨナ坊の位置
ワイリとルツの位置
Race to the coast, the coast!
湾岸を走れ
湾岸
I'll give the orders.
支持は俺が出す
Okay, now beat it! Go! Go!
はいはい行け
GOGO
今の子供　銃持って
Wasn't that kid holding a gun?
It was just a toy.
おもちゃだろ
Just as the rumors claimed,
Orchestra shoots without bias.
噂どおり見境なく撃ちまくる連中だ
オーケストラ
They're pretty dangerous!
相当厄介だぞ
It's only natural for professional killers
人殺しを仕事にしている連中が銃を買ったら
to eagerly use their guns after they buy some.
喜んで使うに決まってる
Even people who have nothing to do with violence
暴力なんて全然関係ない人だって
will grow increasingly unsettled
if you leave a gun in front of them.
目の前に銃があったら
だんだん心が荒れて
And then they'll do something
that surprises even them.
自分でも信じられないような行動をしてしまったりする
That's the type of demonic
power that lies within weapons.
そういう悪魔みたいな力が武器にはあるんだ
ココが売ってるものは　そういうものなんだよ
That's the sort of stuff you sell, Koko.
I'm happy! Jonah, you've
put your feelings into words.
嬉しいよ
ヨナの想いの一つを言葉にしてくれた
I think it's the first time you've done that.
初めて聞けた気がする
There are several points I would like to bring up,
内容には私も言いたいことがいくつかあるが
but we need to find a way out of this mess.
今はこの場をどうしのぐかを考えよう
Killers possessed by those very
demons are currently hunting us down.
悪魔に取り付かれた殺し屋に追われている最中だ
奏でるぜ　千夏
Let's rock, Chinatsu!
As Orchestra, we'll grind the
music of death into our targets!
俺らオーケストラは死の音楽を標的に叩き込む
"Musica ex Machina phase.1"
As Orchestra, we'll grind the
music of death into our targets!
"Musica ex Machina phase.1"
We're artists!
アーティストだ
"Musica ex Machina phase.1"
The ocean god reclines against the light,
光横たえる海神
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
His mistake wavering along the scar
He rises to the surface and takes a breath
浮上して息を継ぎ
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
For he has obtained a love
and hate that only dissolve and blend
His dream leans toward
矛盾孕む
The sound of the scheme
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
That shall encompass this
world fraught with contradictions
脚は　もう無い
He no longer has legs
His heartbeat pierces through the watery wall
水壁を貫く鼓動
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
翻译 TL旧民        日听 yaya
注释 TL旧民        日听 奶昔
后期 aoi           压制 娜夏
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"